Micheal Cutrer

Contact



601.498.4003



mikeycmc73@gmail.com



580 S Pear Orchard Rd Apt 604 Ridgeland, MS

Education

Software Engineering

Jones County Junior College / 2015 - 2020

Software

- Microsoft Office
- Github
- Microsoft Visual Studio& Visual Code

Profile

I am a motivated individual who is capable as well as flexible in multiple situations. I am no stranger to hard work as my experience in a restaraunt has kept me in a high-stress environment allowing me to develop exceptional reasoning, quick thinking, as well as leadership skills.

I have experience in several programming languages including Javascript, RPG, SQL, C++, and others. In addition, I am have active experience in web development using the ExtJs framework to develop web applications.

Skills

- Javascript, C#, Python
- ReactJs, ExtJs, NodeJS
- STRSQL, MySQL

Experience

Walker's Dairy Bar

Crew Member / July 2015 - July 2022

- Crew member and shift leader in charge of leadership, planning, stock and inventory management
- Coordinated large scale catering orders under duress
- Expected to give exceptional customer service and handle all means of orders and transactions

Data Systems Management

Junior Programmer / July 2022 - Current

- \bullet Junior programmer responsible for the creation of web apps as well as converting legacy IBM AS/400 programs into web apps
- Communicated with teammates to solve issues that would arise in production
- Use a mixture of languages to achieve a seamless transition from databases to web apps